Thomas M. Rivers Papers 1887-1963 Mss.B.R52
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1941-1963; 9.5 linear feet
  - The C V Mosby Company (Box 8)
  - Muckenfuss, Ralph (Box 8)
  - Mudd, Stuart (Box 8)
  - Mudge, Gilbert H (Box 8)
  - Müller, Helmut (Box 8)
  - Mundy, J W (Box 8)
  - Mundy, Jessie W,Jr. (Box 8)
  - Munoz, Frank (Box 8)
  - Munson, Donald (Box 8)
  - Murdock, Thomas P (Box 8)
  - Murphy, George E (Box 8)
  - Murphy, Grace K (Box 8)
  - Murphy, James S (Box 8)
  - Murray, E G D (Box 8)
  - Muschenheim, Carl (Box 8)
  - Muscular Dystrophy Associations of America (Box 8)
  - Museum Press, Ltd. (Box 8)
  - Myers, J Norris (Box 8)
  - NAMRU-2 [Naval Medical Research Unit No. 2], 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Nasio, J (Box 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 8)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Box 8)
    - Facsimile of Original Signature Book (Box 8)
    - Presidency (Box 8)
    - Proposals for Nomination (Box 8)
    - Section of Pathology and Microbiology (Box 8)
  - National Broadcasting Company (Box 8)
  - National Committee for Research in Neurological Disorders (Box 8)
  - National Cystic Fibrosis Research Foundation, Philadelphia Chapter (Box 8)
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, Inc., 9 folders (Box 8)
    a.k.a. National Foundation
    - N.F.I.P., Committee on Diagnosis (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Committee on Virus Research (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Fellowships (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Greater New York Chapter (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., March of Dimes (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., March of Dimes, Fulton-DeKalb Chapter (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Specifications and Minimal Requirements for Polio Vaccine, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Recommended Practices...and Questions and Answers About Polio (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Vaccine Advisory Committee/Committee on Virus Research (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Vaccine for Export (Box 8)
    - N.F.I.P., Vaccine Protocols (Box 8)
  - National Foundation for Neuromuscular Diseases (Box 8)
  - National Institutes of Health (Box 8)
    - National Institutes of Health (Box 8)
    - History (Box 8)
    - Minimum Requirements: Polio Vaccine (Box 8)
    - National Microbiological Institute (Box 8)
  - National Jewish Hospital at Denver (Box 8)
  - National League of Nursing Education (Box 9)
  - National Medical Association (Box 9)
  - National Microbiological Institute (Box 9)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 9)
  - National Pet Supply Company (Box 9)
  - National Research Council (Box 9)
    - National Research Council (Box 9)
    - Division of Medical Services (Box 9)
    - Organization and Members (Box 9)
  - National Research Council of Canada (Box 9)
  - National Resources Planning Board (Box 9)
  - National Roster of Scientific and Specialized Personnel (Box 9)
  - National Society for Medical Research (Box 9)
  - Naval Academy Athletic Association (Box 9)
  - Naval Medical Research Institute (Box 9)
  - Naval Reserve Association (Box 9)
  - Navy-Marine Corps Memorial Stadium (Box 9)
  - Nee, Joseph F (Box 9)
  - Neel, James V (Box 9)
  - Nelson, Margorie M (Box 9)
  - Neuberger, Julius (Box 9)
  - Neuman, David L (Box 9)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 9)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 9)
  - New York Cancer Society (Box 9)
  - New York City (Box 9)
    - Board of Health (Box 9)
    - Board of Health, Fluoridation for New York City (Report) (Box 9)
    - Bureau of City Collections (Box 9)
    - Commissioner of Health (Box 9)
    - Convention and Visitors Bureau (Box 9)
    - Department of Health, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Department of Hospitals, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Office of Civil Defense (Box 9)
    - Office of the Mayor (Box 9)
  - New York Clinical Society (Box 9)
  - New York Herald Tribune (Box 9)
  - New York Hospital, Payne-Whitney Committee (Box 9)
  - New York Institute of Clinical Oral Pathology (Box 9)
  - New York Pathological Society (Box 9)
  - New York State, Department of Education (Box 9)
  - New York State, Department of Health (Box 9)
  - New York State, Tax Commission (Box 9)
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association (Box 9)
  - New York University (Box 9)
  - New York University, Seminar for Science Writers (Box 9)
  - New York Zoological Society (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings [Polio Articles by Victor Cohn], 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings -- 3rd International Congress for Microbiology (Box 9)
  - Newsweek Magazine (Box 9)
  - Nickerson, Walter J (Box 9)
  - Niederman, James Corson (Box 9)
  - Nimitz, Chester W. (Box 9)
  - Nishizawa, Y (Box 9)
  - Norby, Gregers (Box 9)
  - Norby, Toke (Box 9)
  - Novak, Emil (Box 9)
  - Ober, Frank R (Box 9)
  - Oberle, Henry (Box 9)
  - O'Connor, Basil (Box 9)
    - O'Connor, Basil, 7 folders (Box 9)
    - The Future of Hospitals (Box 9)
    - 70th Birthday Dinner (Box 9)
  - O'Connor, John J (Box 9)
  - O'Connor and Farber (Box 9)
  - Ochsner Clinic (Box 10)
  - Oehser, Paul H (Box 10)
  - Oester, Y T (Box 10)
  - Ogata, Norio (Box 10)
  - Okano, Kinya (Box 10)
  - The Third Oklahoma Conference on Handicapped Children (Box 10)
  - Olitsky, Peter K (Box 10)
  - Oliver, Wade W (Box 10)
  - Olsen, Herluf (Box 10)
  - Opie, Eugene L (Box 10)
  - Oppel, Theodore W (Box 10)
  - Oppenheimer, Robert (Box 10)
  - Osterhout, W J V (Box 10)
  - Overman, John R (Box 10)
  - Owen, Philip (Box 10)
  - Packard, Arthur W (Box 10)
  - Page, Irvine H (Box 10)
  - Page, Robertson (Box 10)
  - Palmer, George (Box 10)
  - Palmer, Walter W (Box 10)
  - Pan American Health Organization (Box 10)
  - Park, Barbara (Box 10)
  - Park, Edwards A (Box 10)
  - Parker, Robert F (Box 10)
  - Parker and Son (Box 10)
  - Parr, Leland W (Box 10)
  - Parshley, Mary S (Box 10)
  - Passano Foundation (Box 10)
  - Paton, R Townley (Box 10)
  - Patterson, Robert P (Box 10)
  - Paul, John Rodman (Box 10)
  - Paullin, James E (Box 10)
  - Pearlman, Ely (Box 10)
  - Pearson, J C (Box 10)
  - Pett, Max M (Box 10)
  - Peking Union Medical School (Box 10)
  - Penniman, Howard R (Box 10)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 10)
  - Perspectives in Biology (Box 10)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine (Box 10)
  - Perspectives in Virology I (Box 10)
  - Perspectives in Virology II (Box 10)
  - Perspecties in Virology III, [1962] (Box 10)
  - Peterson, E H (Box 10)
  - Charles Pfizer and Co. (Box 10)
  - Phillips, R A (Box 10)
  - Phillips, Robert A (Box 10)
  - Phillips, William R (Box 10)
  - Pinkerton, Henry (Box 10)
  - Pittman, Jean (Box 10)
  - Pittsburg Zoological Gardens (Box 10)
  - Plates (from publications) (Box 10)
  - Polani, Paul E (Box 10)
  - Polio Vaccine Field Trial (Box 10)
  - Polio Vaccine - Oral, Live - Reading List (Box 10)
  - Poliomyelitis Vaccine: Specifications and Minimum Requirements -, 1954; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Poliomyelitis Vaccines: Status and Prospect (Box 10)
  - Pollak, Ann (Box 10)
  - Pollard, Morris (Box 10)
  - Pool, E H (Box 10)
  - Pool, J Lawrence (Box 10)
  - Pool, John L (Box 10)
  - Post Office Department, Office of Inspector (Box 10)
  - Powell, Vernon E (Box 10)
  - Powers, William F (Box 10)
  - Practitioners' Society of New York (Box 10)
  - Presbyterian Hospital (Box 10)
  - Presidents' Committee on Employment of the Physically handicapped (Box 10)
  - Preston, David R (Box 10)
  - Price, David E (Box 10)
  - Priest, J Percy (Box 10)
  - Progreso Médico (Box 10)
  - Progress of Science (Box 10)
  - Project Hope (Box 10)
  - Protest to the American Medical Association (Box 10)
  - Protein Foundation, Inc. (Box 10)
  - Protoplasmatologia (Box 10)
  - Provisional Committee Against Imposition of `Loyalty' Oaths for Physicians (Box 10)
  - Prudential Insurance Company of America (Box 10)
  - Public Affairs Committee (Box 10)
  - Public Health Association (Box 10)
  - Public Health Research Institute, 7 folders (Box 10)
  - Public Health Research Institute, 8 folders (Box 11)
  - Public Health Service - Division of International Health (Box 11)
  - Puck, Theodore T (Box 11)
  - Putnam, Tracy J (Box 11)
  - Quarton, T B (Box 11)
  - Quebec Province, Ministry of Mines and Fisheries (Box 11)
  - Quickel, Kenneth E (Box 11)
  - Quinn, David H (Box 11)
  - Quinn, Edward L (Box 11)
  - Radioear (Box 11)
  - Radziowanowski, Stephanie (Box 11)
  - Ragland, Tillie (Box 11)
  - Ragoczy, L (Box 11)
  - Rapalski, Adam (Box 11)
  - Rappleye, Willard C (Box 11)
  - Rasmussen, A F (Box 11)
  - Ratner, Sarah (Box 11)
  - Ray, Bronson S (Box 11)
  - Rea, Walter B (Box 11)
  - Walter Reed Army Institute of Research (Box 11)
  - Walter Reed Society (Box 11)
  - Respirators (Box 11)
  - Registered Nurses Association (Box 11)
  - Reichert, Dr. and Mrs. F L (Box 11)
  - Reid, Mrs. Ogden (Box 11)
  - Reimann, Hobart A (Box 11)
  - Renshaw, Dr. (Box 11)
  - Renshaw, Janet (Box 11)
  - Rhine, Margaret (Box 11)
  - Rhodes, George K (Box 11)
  - Rhoads, C P (Box 11)
  - Rhoads, Jonathan E (Box 11)
  - Rich, Arnold Rice (Box 11)
  - Richards, Dickinson W (Box 11)
  - Richardson, D (Box 11)
  - Richmond see: City of Richmond, Dept. of Public Health (Box 11)
  - Richter, Maurice N (Box 11)
  - Riley, Harris D (Box 11)
  - Rivers Family (Box 11)
  - Rivers, Mrs. A B (Box 11)
  - Rivers, Alonzo B (Box 11)
  - Rivers, Teresa J. (Mrs. Thomas M.) (Box 11)
  - Rivers, Thomas Milton (Box 11)
    - Rivers, Thomas Milton (Box 11)
    - Rivers, Thomas M. Answers to Queries and Minor Notes (Box 11)
    - AMA Journal (Box 11)
    - Behind the Scenes in Virus Research - Requests for Reprints (Box 11)
    - Bibliography (Box 11)
    - Big City Meeting, (1959) (Box 11)
    - Biographical Materials, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Blood Cultures, Measles (Box 11)
    - The Carrier Problem in Infectious Diseases (Box 11)
    - Certain Aspects of Pathological Lesions Caused by Viruses (Box 11)
    - Certain Public Health Aspects of Infectious Diseases, (1947) (Box 11)
    - Chart of Disease, (1926) (Box 11)
    - Concepts and Methods of Medical Research, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - Critique of Knowledge Concerning Filterable Viruses (Box 11)
    - Diplomas, etc. (Box 11)
    - Discussion of W. H. Park's Paper, (1927) (Box 11)
    - Discussion of Papers of Poliomyelitis, (1935) (Box 11)
    - Effect of Repeated Freezing and Thawing on Bacilli and Viruses (Box 11)
    - Encephalitis (Box 11)
    - Epidemic Diseases (Box 11)
    - Epidemiology (Box 11)
    - Establishment and Activities of U.S. Naval Medical Research Unit No. 2 in the Pacific (Box 11)
    - Etiology, Pathology and Prevention of Measles (Box 11)
    - Experimental Infection of the Skin with Hemolytic Streptococci (Box 11)
    - Filterable Viruses - A Critical Review (Box 12)
    - The Future of Virus Research (Box 12)
    - Health Through Conflict (Box 12)
    - History of U.S. Naval Medical Research Unit No. 2., 3 folders (Box 12)
    - History of NAMRU-2, Plates and Photos, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - The Infinitely Small in Biology (Box 12)
    - Interview - The New Polio Vaccine (Box 12)
    - Killed-Virus vs. Live-Virus Vaccines Against Polio (Box 12)
    - Laboratory Reports (Box 12)
    - Letters Congratulatory on Appointment As Director of Rockefeller Institute Hospital, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - The Life History of Cancer (Box 12)
    - Life Insurance Policy (Box 12)
    - Local Passive Immunity (Box 12)
    - Making Viruses Work for Man (Box 12)
    - Medical Research, 1909-2009 (Box 12)
    - Microbiology and Immunization: A Summary, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 12)
    - The Nature of Viruses (Box 12)
    - Predicting Results in Research (Box 12)
    - Programs and Aims of the National Foundation (Box 12)
    - Proposed Plan for Study of Poliomyelitis (Box 12)
    - The Public Health Research Institute (Box 12)
    - Quarantine in the Control of Polio (Box 12)
    - Recent Advances in the Treatment of Viral and Rickettsial Diseases, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Recent Developments in Research on Polio and Other Viruses (Box 12)
    - Relation of Medical Research to Clinical Practice and Public Health (Box 12)
    - Relationship and Reactions of Host Cells to Viruses, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Remarks Concerning My Trip to South America, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Remarks Concerning the Nature of Viruses (Box 12)
    - Report of Work on the Isolation Service, (1929) (Box 13)
    - Report of the Board of Scientific Directors, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Research and the Expanded Program, A Vision of the Future, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Research in the Expanded Program of the National Foundation (Box 13)
    - Respiratory Diseases (Box 13)
    - Responsibilities in the Development of Polio Vaccine (Box 13)
    - Review of Encephalitis: A Clinical Study (Box 13)
    - The Scientific Spirit (Box 13)
    - Some General Aspects of the Filterable Viruses, 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Speech at Dr. Cole's Dinner, 1938 (Box 13)
    - Speech for Tenth Anniversary of National Foundation (Box 13)
    - Statement of Virus Research for Voice of America (Box 13)
    - The Story of Research on Poliomyelitis, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Studies Concerning Chicken-pox (Box 13)
    - Studies Concerning Chicken-Pox and Erysipeals (Box 13)
    - Studies on Chicken-pox -, 1923 (Box 13)
    - Studies on Chicken-pox -, 1924 (Box 13)
    - Studies on Varicella, Introduction (Draft) (Box 13)
    - Studies on Varicella, Susceptibility of Rabbits to Virus (Box 13)
    - Talk to South Jersey Medical Research Foundation (Box 13)
    - Trends in Research on Polio and other Viruses (Box 13)
    - A Trip to South America, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Ultraviolet Light and Vaccine Virus (Box 13)
    - Unknown (Box 13)
    - Varicella in Monkeys (Box 13)
    - The Virus: A Key to Medicine's Future (Box 13)
    - Virus de Vejez, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Los Virus Filtrables en general y el virus de la psitacosis en particular, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Viruses -, 1932 (Box 13)
    - Where Research is Leading, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - [World War I Papers], 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Rivers, Berry, Benjamin, Sprunt: Report on Infection -, 1930 (Box 14)
    - Report on Infection -, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Rivers and Eldridge: Clinical Study of Chicken-pox and Measles (Box 14)
  - Rivers and Hoagland: Therapy of Infectious Hepatitis, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Rivers, Thomas M and Teresa J. Income Tax Returns, (12), 1942-1953 (Box 14)
  - Rivers, ed. Viral and Rickettsial Infections of Man -- Revisions (Box 14)
  - Robbins, William J (Box 14)
  - Robertson, Albert D (Box 14)
  - Robertson, Dr. and Mrs. O H (Box 14)
  - Robins, John C, Jr. (Box 14)
  - Robinson, Frank H (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller, Abby A (Mrs. John D) (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller, David (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller, John D (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller, John D, Jr., 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller, John D, 3rd (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller Hospital, Nursing Staff (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller Institute (Box 14)
    - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - By-Laws and Resolutions (Box 14)
    - Faculty and Student Club (Box 14)
    - Hospital, "Report of a Fire" (Box 14)
    - International Health Division (Box 14)
    - Minutes of Board Meetings, 14 folders (Box 14-15)
    - Press (Box 15)
    - Public Relations (Box 15)
    - Report of the Hospital, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Roe, Isabelle (Box 15)
  - Roehm, H (Box 15)
  - Rohm and Haas Company (Box 15)
  - Romeyn, J A (Box 15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D (Box 15)
  - Rosborough, Jean (Box 15)
  - Rossi, Mayor Angelo (Box 15)
  - Roswell Park Memorial Institute (Box 15)
  - Royal Medical Society (Box 15)
  - Royal Society of Medicine (Box 15)
  - Rusk, Dean (Box 15)
  - Rusk, Howard A (Box 15)
  - Rutgers University, Institute of Microbiology (Box 15)
  - Rutgers University Press (Box 15)
  - Ryan, Stephen V (Box 15)
  - Sabin, Albert B (Box 15)
    - Sabin, Albert B, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - The Herpes Group of Viruses, Recommendations for Classification, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Present Status of a [Polio] Vaccine, 1953 (Box 15)
  - Dr. Florence R. Sabin Memorial Fund (Box 15)
  - Safe Deposit and Trust Company (Box 15)
  - Salk, Jonas E., ca. 1954-1960; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Critique of AMA Report on "Present State in U.S.", 1961; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995 (Box 15)
  - Critique... Summary Statement, 1961; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995 (Box 15)
  - Press Conference, 1961; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995 (Box 15)
  - Specifications and Minimal Requirements for Polio Vaccine, 1953; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995 (Box 15)
  - Polio Vaccine Preparation and Administration, 1959; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995 (Box 15)
  - Formaldehyde Treatment of Polio Vaccines, n.d.; Salk, Jonas et al. (Box 15)
  - Salk Institute (Box 15)
  - Salvioli, G (Box 15)
  - Sanders, Murray (Box 15)
  - Sanders, Mrs. Roberts West (Box 15)
  - Sanna, Antonio (Box 15)
  - Sano, Ichiro (Box 15)
  - Supero, J J (Box 15)
  - Sauls, H. Cliff (Box 15)
  - W. B. Saunders Co. (Box 15)
  - Saverso, Anthony P, Jr. (Box 15)
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A (Box 15)
  - Scanga, Franco (Box 15)
  - Schaad, Howard (Box 15)
  - Schafer, W (Box 15)
  - Shaffer-Epstein, Stella (Box 15)
  - Schatz, Harry A (Box 15)
  - Scheele, Leonard A (Box 15)
  - Schenley Distillers Corp. (Box 15)
  - Schiffer, Sydney (Box 16)
  - Schlesinger, R Walter (Box 16)
  - Schultz, Fred W (Box 16)
  - Schultz, Dr. and Mrs. E W (Box 16)
  - Schmeisser, Harry Christian (Box 16)
  - Schimdt, Louis (Box 16)
  - Schmidt, Reginald M (Box 16)
  - Schroeder, Henry A (Box 16)
  - Schulman, Adele (Box 16)
  - Schwentker, Francis F (Box 16)
  - Science Museum (Box 16)
  - Science Service (Box 16)
  - Scientific American (Box 16)
  - Scott, T F McNair (Box 16)
  - Seaman, Louis Livingston, Fund (Box 16)
  - Sebrell, W A,Jr. (Box 16)
  - Seelye, Gilbert T (Box 16)
  - Seidenfeld (Box 16)
  - Seldin, S Daniel (Box 16)
  - Sellers, T F (Box 16)
  - Seykens, P W A (Box 16)
  - Shackleton, Robert W (Box 16)
  - Shanks, Edgar D (Box 16)
  - Shannon, James A (Box 16)
  - Shapiro, John L (Box 16)
  - Shawki, Ibrahim Bex - Polio in Cairo (Box 16)
  - Shay, Donald E (Box 16)
  - Shedlovsky, Theodore (Box 16)
  - Sheraton-Baltimore Inn (Box 16)
  - Sherman, H C (Box 16)
  - Sherman, Hoyt (Box 16)
  - Sherman, James M (Box 16)
  - Sherwood, Noble P (Box 16)
  - Shingler, George P (Box 16)
  - Shope, Dr. Richard E (Box 16)
  - [Shope's Paper on Immunization -, 1955] (Box 16)
  - Shorney, Brian (Box 16)
  - Shotwell, Willets H, Jr. (Box 16)
  - Shwartzman, Gregory (Box 16)
  - Sigma Nu Fraternity (Box 16)
  - Simmons, J O (Box 16)
  - Simmons, James Stevens (Box 16)
  - Singher, H O (Box 16)
  - Slemons, C C (Box 16)
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute (Box 16)
  - Smadel, Joseph E (Box 16)
  - Smillie, Wilson G (Box 16)
  - Smith, Carter (Box 16)
  - Smith, David T (Box 16)
  - Smith, Geddes (Box 16)
  - Smith, Harold V (Box 16)
  - Smith, Kenneth W (Box 16)
  - Smith, Kline and French Laboratories (Box 16)
  - Smith, Marie (Box 16)
  - Smithsonian Institution (Box 16)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Editorial Division (Box 16)
  - Smorodintsev, Anatol A (Box 16)
  - Snyder, Alice (Box 16)
  - Snyder, John C (Box 16)
  - Snyder, William F (Box 16)
  - Society of American Bacteriologists (Box 16)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine (Box 16)
  - Society for the Rehabilitation of the Facially Disfigured (Box 16)
  - Society of the Sigma Xi, Rockefeller Institute Chapter (Box 16)
  - Sockman, Ralph W (Box 16)
  - Sonnenberg, Florence (Box 16)
  - Soper, Fred L (Box 16)
  - South Jersey Medical Research Foundation (Box 16)
  - Southwood, A R (Box 16)
  - Southworth, Hamilton (Box 16)
  - Souza-Araujo, H C de (Box 16)
  - Edward Sparrow Hospital (Box 16)
    General note
    5-3
  - Spaulding, Alice Stewart (Box 16)
  - Spaulding, Earle H (Box 16)
  - Spencer, Steven M: The Germs Are Smart, Too. (Box 16)
  - Spring, William C, Jr. (Box 16)
  - Sprunt, Douglas H (Box 16)
  - Stankowski, R J (Box 16)
  - Stanley, Wendell M (Box 16)
  - Starr, Lilian (Box 16)
  - State of California - Department of Public Health (Box 16)
  - State of Georgia, Department of Public Health (Box 16)
  - State of Illinois, Department of Public Health (Box 16)
  - State of New Jersey, Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 16)
  - State of Oregon, Board of Health (Box 16)
  - Stebbins, Ernest L (Box 16)
  - Steele, J Murray (Box 16)
  - Steele, Sylvia (Box 16)
  - Stegen, Edward F (Box 16)
  - Stein, M Theiss (Box 16)
  - Stein, William (Box 16)
  - Stern, Gustav (Box 16)
  - Stetten, Dewitt, Jr. (Box 16)
  - Stevens, Elsie R (Box 16)
  - Stevenson, Frank E (Box 16)
  - Stickney, Stonewall B (Box 16)
  - Stillman, E. G. (Box 16)
  - Stimson, Philip M (Box 16)
  - Stokes, Joseph (Box 16)
  - Stoll, Norman R (Box 16)
  - Stritehoff, Nelson H (Box 16)
  - Stroul, Edith (Box 16)
  - Stuart, William M (Box 16)
  - Sugar Research Foundation (Box 16)
  - Sulzberger, Marion B (Box 16)
  - Swift, Homer F (Box 16)
  - Swift, Homer F, The Early Days of the Hospital (Box 16)
  - Symposium on Congenital Malformations -, 1961 (Box 16)
  - Symposium on Psittacosis (Box 16)
  - Syverton, Jerome T (Box 16)
  - Syverton, Mrs. Mildred (Box 16)
  - Szaboó, Zoltan (Box 16)
  - Taipei International Women's Club (Box 16)
  - Taliaferro, W H (Box 16)
  - Tamm, Igor (Box 16)
  - Tan, Minoru (Box 16)
  - Tappan, Benjamin (Box 16)
  - Tatum, Edward Lawrie -- Importance of Basic Research (Box 16)
  - Taylor, Calvin W (Box 16)
  - Taylor, Grant (Box 16)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA) (Box 16)
  - Teagle, Walter C (Box 16)
  - TenBroeck, Carl (Box 16)
  - Ten Eyck, Mrs. Maude E (Box 16)
  - Tenney, Charles F (Box 16)
  - The Teratology Society (Box 16)
  - Terry, Luther L (Box 16)
  - Thalhimer, William (Box 16)
  - Thayer, John B (Box 16)
  - Therapy of Infectious Hepatitis (Box 16)
  - Thomas, Addie (Box 16)
  - Thornton, H Gerard (Box 16)
  - Thornton, Lawson (Box 16)
  - Tillet, William S (Box 16)
  - Tillotson, Brian T (Box 16)
  - Time Magazine (Box 16)
  - Tiselius, Arne (Box 16)
  - Tissue Culture Association (Box 16)
  - Toll, Robert M (Box 17)
  - Topping, Norman (Box 17)
  - Toy Manufacturers of the U.S.A. (Box 17)
  - Traeger, Cornelius (Box 17)
  - Tratado Internacional de Gastroenterologia (Box 17)
  - Trefflich, Henry (Box 17)
  - Troan, John (Box 17)
  - Troyer, Maurice E (Box 17)
  - Trudeau, Francis (Box 17)
  - Tui, Co (Box 17)
  - Turner, R G (Box 17)
  - Turner, Mr. and Mrs. R G (Box 17)
  - Turner, Thomas B (Box 17)
  - Turner, Victor R, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Tuskegee Institute (Box 17)
  - Twenty-one Club Menu -, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Tydings, Jen (Box 17)
  - Tyler, Joseph R (Box 17)
  - Tyrrell, David (Box 17)
  - Underwood's Account of Infantile Paralysis -, 1789 (Box 17)
  - United Kingdom Scientific Mission (Box 17)
  - United States Army, The Surgeon General (Box 17)
  - United States Civil Service Commission (Box 17)
  - United States Civil Service Examiners Board (Box 17)
  - United States Department of Commerce (Box 17)
  - U.S. Department of Defense, Research and Development Board, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 17)
  - U.S., Department of the Navy (Box 17)
    - U.S., Department of the Navy (Box 17)
    - Bureau of Medicine and Surgery (Box 17)
    - Final Orders and USNR Papers for T.M. Rivers, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous World War II Memos (Box 17)
    - Rivers' Promotion to Rear Admiral... (Box 17)
  - U.S. Department of State (Box 17)
  - U.S., Federal Security Agency, Public Health Service (Box 17)
  - U.S. Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 17)
  - United States Information Agency (Box 17)
  - United States Internal revenue Service (Box 17)
  - U.S., IRS, Special Narcotic Stamp Tax (Box 17)
  - U.S. Naval Reserve, Naval Reserve Training Center (Box 17)
  - U.S. Naval Reserve Association (Box 17)
  - U.S. Navy, Headquarters, Guam (Box 17)